{
    "subject": "resource/Buffalo_Bill_Ranch",
    "predicate": "ontology/governingBody",
    "object": "resource/Nebraska_Game_and_Parks_Commission",
    "human_readable": "The governing body of Buffalo Bill Ranch is Nebraska Game and Parks Commission.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8803929090499878,
            "question": "Who oversees the Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8557794094085693,
            "question": "Which Nebraska organization manages Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.851704478263855,
            "question": "Which entity governs the Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7584716081619263,
            "question": "What body has jurisdiction over Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7260845303535461,
            "question": "What group has authority over the operations of Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6982830166816711,
            "question": "Which organization maintains Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6804752945899963,
            "question": "What organization is responsible for managing Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6194161772727966,
            "question": "Who is responsible for the upkeep and management of Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5546230673789978,
            "question": "Who is in charge of the Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.48916542530059814,
            "question": "What entity ensures the preservation of Buffalo Bill Ranch?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The governing body of Buffalo Bill Ranch is Nebraska Game and Parks Commission.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8108_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is in charge of the Buffalo Bill Ranch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8108_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is responsible for the upkeep and management of Buffalo Bill Ranch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8108_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What organization is responsible for managing Buffalo Bill Ranch?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8108_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_93.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8108_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis indicates that the triple \"The governing body of Buffalo Bill Ranch is Nebraska Game and Parks Commission\" is supported by the information in the documents. In particular, the document at file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_8108/re-ranker-msmarco/39.txt states that \"The 4,000-acre ranch was sold in 1911 and has been under the management of the Nebraska Game and Parks Commission since 1964.\" which implies that the governing body is indeed the Nebraska Game and Parks Commission."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information provided in the documents states, \"The 4,000-acre ranch was sold in 1911 and has been under the management of the Nebraska Game and Parks Commission since 1964.\" This supports the statement that the governing body of Buffalo Bill Ranch is the Nebraska Game and Parks Commission."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}